What if your deepest regrets manifested as something terrifying?
A group was told to stay put, tasked with tending to the sick, but fear held them captive.
One of them, a specter, emerged, an effigy of Sebastian sent to Lure Helen.
This ghost rallied more spectres fueled by the guilt of the people of New Eden.
It was the anguish of the dead, their suffering twisted by a cruel leader's denial.
He chose to inflict pain on others rather than confront his own darkness.
Will this cycle of torment ever end?
What truly unleashed the darkness upon New Eden?
A woman cried out, bound in chains, her pleas ignored.
This silence ignited a curse, a creeping dread that gripped the town.
Years later, a tragedy struck the mind, a disaster whispered to be her vengeful act.
Now, a leader is needed, one untainted by this dark past.
Yet the path back to New Eden is blocked, the town consumed by fear and hatred for what it cannot comprehend.
The only hope lies in finding answers, perhaps from a woman named Grace,
and laying the past to rest before the void claims them all.
What forgotten sin still haunts New Eden?
Did she send him into the woods to die?
He sought a hidden treasure, a fortune promised by old maps,
but the land yielded only rot and despair.
His brother claimed the prize,
a act of betrayal that sealed his fate.
Now a dark ritual looms.
What truly happened in that cursed cabin, and who is grace,
is the teacher a phantom or a manipulator.
The camp trembles, threatened by a past that refuses to stay buried.
What secrets lie within those woods?
Tell us your theories below.